Finding Aid for the Martin Perlich Interviews PASC-M.0341
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Interviews, Series 1.
  - Ung, Chinary, 2006 January 19; compact disc (Box 5)
    Subject is a composer.
  - Upshaw, Dawn, 2003 March 12; minidisc (Box 4)
    Subject is a singer.
  - Valencia, Rita, 2007 April 19; compact disc (Box 8)
    On disc, "distorted."
  - Verrett, Shirley, 2003 August 6; DAT (Box 8)
    Subject is an American operatic singer.
  - Vidal, Gore, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Vidal, Gore, 1988 December 8; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Duration: 41:17
  - Viver Brasil, 2006 June 30; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Viver Brasil, 2007 September 4; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Viver Brasil, 2007 September 1; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 31:12.
  - von der Schmidt, Jeff, 2006 January 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - von der Schmidt, Jeff, 2006 June 29; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Von der Schmidt, Jeff, 2005 December 15; compact disc (Box 7)
  - von der Schmidt, Jeff, 2004 March 3; DAT (Box 8)
  - Von Stade, Frederica, 2003 January 16; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Von Stade, Frederica, compact disc (Box 8)
  - Waites, Althea, DAT (Box 6)
  - Waits, Tom, 1978 December 18; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Walden, Chris, 2008 May 20; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Waldman, Wendy, 1977 November 21; audio cassette (Box 4)
    On item, "Topanga."
  - Waldman, Wendy, 1978 July 26; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Walton, audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Watts, Andre, 2004 May 3; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Watts, Andre, 2002 Feburary 13; minidisc (Box 9)
  - Weathers, Carl, 1978 March 23; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Weddell, Mimi, 2008 April 11; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Weddell, Mimi, 2008 April 11; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Hats Off."
  - Welch, Bob, 1979 June 6; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Wheelwright, Reverend Farley, 1971 March 14; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Whitacre, Eric, 2006 March 21; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Whitacre, Eric, 2006 April 1; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Winkler, Henry, 2007 March 9; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Winkler, Henry, 2007 August 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:45.
  - Wispelluey, Pieter, 2003 May 2; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Worby, Rachael, 2007 July 17; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Worby, Rachel, 2007 July 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Wurman, Alex, 2005 July 15; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Yablon, Sharon, 2007 February 20; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Yablon, Sharon, 2007 March 1; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 27:38.
  - Young, Jessie Colin, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Young, Robina, 2003 April 16; DAT (Box 6)
  - Ysaye Quartet, 2003 November 10; DAT (Box 6)
  - Zappa, Frank, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Zappa, Frank, 1972; DAT (Box 6)
  - Zappa, Frank, 1972; DAT (Box 8)
  - Zappa, Frank, compact disc (Box 8)
    On disc, "02 ... research."
  - Zappa, Frank, 1979 August 16; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Taped at Joe's Garage.
  - Zappa, Frank, 1979 April 19; audio cassette (Box 10)
    On container, "Jewish Princess."
  - Zappa, Frank, 1988 October 12; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Zebrowski, Marek, 2006 October 11; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Zevon, Warren, 1978 February 6; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Zevon, Warren, 1977 August 30; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Zimmerman, Guy, 2005 July 6; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Zimmerman, Guy, 2005 July 25; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:35.
  - Zinman, David, 1990 August 3; audio cassette (Box 12)
    Duration: 24:03